Does this mean I managed to make the world a peaceful place?
Oh, cool. You're already awake. Good morning, big brother.
Coterie, you're all right. What about Fraxinus? How's the crew? Is everyone okay?
Is it possible you're still asleep?
Uh, no, I'm... Hold on. What day is it?
Huh? It's the 3rd of November, don't you know that?
If it's November 3rd, then... It's the day after Origami went inverse.
Thank goodness. What a relief.
What the heck? What's happening?
I did it. I managed to change the world after all.
Daily life. On the surface, we think we know what it is.
Then, reality rears its head, and we discover all is not as it seems.
No way.
Well, it reminds me as follows.
Nah.
I want to see...
We'll be right back.
Isn't that what you said you'd make yesterday, or am I not remembering right?
Yesterday?
Oh, right, I did.
Sorry.
Didn't end up having those ingredients.
So I made you a rice bowl.
With sweet eggs, too.
Oh, my God.
That sounds so good right now.
Oh, I mean, I literally...
Does this world have a whole different history that I'm not aware of?
Well, what a nice morning.
It was good of you to pick me up, servant.
Salutations.
Good morning, everyone.
Shido, Toka, Coterie.
Yeah, hey.
Morning.
What's with you?
If I didn't know better for a second there, I would have sworn you were totally checking out our boobs.
Explanation.
While gross, it still isn't an unheard of reaction for a man.
Care to add anything, Shido?
Nope.
I'm good.
Thanks.
Origami hasn't shown up yet.
Uh, what's the matter?
I don't know.
I can't explain it.
It's as if something is incomplete.
Just kind of a weird feeling.
Incomplete?
Welcome.
Good morning, everyone.
Suzuhara?
Here.
Satoshi?
Is she absent today?
Here.
Or maybe she's just running late.
Next is Tonomachi?
Yo!
Hiroto Tonomachi is present and accounted for and ready to face the day, my love.
Right.
So, Tonomachi is very much present.
Next is Nakahara?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Did I say something weird or are you just having a moment?
Um, no, I'm...
Her name should come after Tonomachi's.
Sorry, but what about Origami?
Who's Origami?
I don't think I've ever known anyone by that name.
Huh?
Origami?
What the heck kind of name is that?
What, did Itsuka, like, fold a bunch of paper cranes for the teacher?
Ugh!
Hold on, does he think you can steal my Tammy with arts and crafts?
That's so lame.
Oh, I see.
I guess, here in this reality, Origami doesn't live in the city.
The Origami of this world probably doesn't hold a grudge against spirits.
She's just off somewhere living happily with her parents.
It's better this way.
This is how it always should have been.
Shiro?
What's up, Toka?
Are you alright?
Is something bothering you?
Oh, no, I'm fine.
I hope that she's happy.
Though, I would have loved to see her again, even just once.
To see this new Origami, smiling.
What's going on?
Is he okay?
Yeah, seems like he's in the dumps.
Look at how zoned out he is.
Has to be a girl.
What do you mean?
Why do you think that?
I mean, I might be wrong, so don't get your panties all in a twist.
Hey, if you know, out with this!
It's just that when it comes to the troubles of high school boys,
you can lay money down on it being about some girl.
Someone treating them badly or not reciprocating their feelings.
Typical guys worry about these things all the time.
Really?
They worry about that stuff, too?
Yeah, even though when you ask if they want to group up for a project,
they say, ew, and try to act all disgusted.
And when you pick up their eraser,
they say you can just keep it now that you've touched it or something dumb.
Hold on, back up a minute.
How the heck does a spirit like you know so much about student life anyway?
Uh, listen.
The point is, I think it's obvious that something happened to him at school.
He'll probably be fine if we give him time, but I can't help but worry.
Me too.
It's tough seeing Shido acting so depressed like this.
Isn't there anything we can do for him?
I don't know what to tell you.
I'll say one thing.
If it's girl trouble that's giving Shido grief,
then the only thing to heal his heart is another girl.
Oops, too close.
Man, I'm kind of focused.
Hey, Shido.
Need some help?
Huh?
Sure, thank you.
Why don't you wash...
What kind of outfits are those?
And what's with those bodies?
What?
We all have a body.
What's the problem?
Yeah, she's right.
Don't think about that right now.
What's important is that we help.
Right?
It's just that, um...
Patsumi!
Was this your idea?
Maybe it was.
Maybe it wasn't.
Wait a damn second.
Why aren't you in a bathing suit like the two of us?
I thought we all agreed that we'd get dressed up together.
It's true, we did.
But once I thought about it, I realized that wearing that would be super embarrassing.
I was afraid I might feel stupid, you know?
Girl, you're the one who gave us these stupid outfits!
You little...
Get over here!
I'll dress you myself to calm down!
I'm being violated!
You guys!
Would you please knock it off?
Huh?
Uh, pal, that was rough.
Everyone good?
You guys are killing me, you know?
Well, I'm sorry about that.
I apologize, Shido.
Yeah, sorry.
No worries.
I'm sorry that I had you all concerned.
Thank you.
I really am better now.
I don't mean to pry into your business or anything, but man, get a hold of yourself.
After all, you never know when another spirit is going to appear, right?
Yeah.
There are spirits we don't know about.
Not to mention the fact that Kurumi and Devil are out there.
Wait, who's Devil?
I don't know that spirit.
What are you talking about?
I mean the spirit hunter, Devil?
And if you thought that Nightmare was bad, this one can be every bit as dangerous.
As bad as Kurumi?
Are you for real right now?
What the heck's with you today, Shido?
It's almost as if you've forgotten everything up until yesterday.
Sorry.
Could she go over some info again?
The stuff about this spirit named Devil.
Fine.
We've confirmed she exists, but she's an unidentified spirit who's evaded all attempts at contact so far.
Also, not surprisingly, I'd say, Devil's an inverse.
Wait, what do you mean?
An inverse spirit just shows up here sometimes?
Well, I'm trying to tell you.
We don't know very much about her yet.
Tell me this, though.
What's a spirit hunter?
It's just like it sounds.
Devil never shows up anywhere on her own.
She only appears whenever another spirit manifests itself.
Then, suddenly, she's there and she attacks them.
If Toka and the others hadn't helped her out, Natsumi would have been in big trouble.
Wait a minute.
Is this her?
Yeah.
Horikami.
Shido, are you still sleepy?
No, I'm okay.
I just didn't get much rest last night.
Oh.
Where is Horikami?
She wasn't in her apartment.
And she wasn't at the house where she lived with her parents, either.
Why did she become a spirit?
Why an inverse?
By changing history five years ago, I should have saved her mom and dad.
Good morning, everybody.
I have an idea.
Let's go all out today.
What happened during that five-year span?
What could have changed?
Oh, I almost forgot.
I can't do much alone.
Maybe if I explain what I know, Ratatasker will look into it.
If I could have your attention, today I have a new friend to introduce to you all.
Go ahead.
Come on in, please.
I'm Horikami Tobiiichi.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you, everyone.
Look at that dazzling long hair and that pure, innocent smile.
She's cute enough to give my honey a run for her money.
Well, let's see.
It looks like the seat next to Itsuka is open.
Please feel free to sit there.
Sure, thanks.
No way.
Don't I know you?
What do you mean?
What makes you think Devil transferred to your school?
I'll explain it later, once I'm back home.
I swear it's true.
You have to believe me.
All right.
But I admit, I'm not thoroughly convinced.
I get it.
I'll have Ratatasker investigate.
What's the student's name?
Origami.
Last name Tobiiichi.
Hold on.
Do you mean Origami Tobiiichi from the AST?
Wait.
Coterie, do you remember the last world?
What are you talking about?
I know her because she fought against Toka and the others a bunch of times.
She retired not too long ago.
Now that you mention it, it does seem like Tobiiichi left the AST around the same time Devil first started appearing regularly.
Why did Origami join the AST?
I saved her parents.
Are you even listening?
Sorry, yeah.
Just tell me if you find out anything.
I don't get it.
If I changed what happened five years ago, then why would she...
Guess I'm gonna have to ask her in person.
Was this for me?
Did you want to talk about something?
Yeah.
Sorry to bother you, Origami.
Thank you.
Oops.
Sorry.
We haven't met yet.
I guess it's kind of rude to talk as if I know you.
No.
I just wasn't expecting my first name.
And you're...
Itsuka, right?
What is this about?
A question.
When you saw me this morning, did you try to ask me something?
Oh.
Sorry if that's been bothering you.
It's just that I was a little surprised.
The thing is, you look just like someone I met a long time ago.
You mean, could we have...
No, I don't think we've met.
The person I'm referring to I saw around five years ago.
You would have been in elementary school.
Besides.
That person actually passed away.
Five years ago.
Right before my eyes.
Oh my gosh.
She means me.
So, shouldn't we go back to class now?
Uh, wait.
Hold on a sec.
Five years ago.
This didn't happen during the Nanko area fire, did it?
How did you know that?
Oh gosh.
Could that have been your older brother that I saw that day?
Well, something like that.
What is it?
Oh, I owe him everything.
Your brother saved both of my parents' lives.
If he hadn't been there, my mom and dad would have both died for sure.
I'm forever grateful.
Oh, sure.
That confirms it.
Sounds like I was able to save Origami's parents after all.
Ah, sorry for blurting that out.
No, it's okay.
I am so thankful for what he did for them that day.
Even though, as fate would have it, my parents then died in a car accident a year later.
No.
But thanks to your wonderful brother, that last year they were alive,
my mom and dad were able to give me so much love and happiness.
Wow, I'm glad.
Is that the hand of fate at work?
Are you okay?
Well, I was kind of wondering why you joined the AST.
I mean, since they survived.
Wait, how did you know about that?
Oh, I don't know. I just, uh...
Did you go outside?
In the middle of a spatial quake alarm?
You know you're not allowed to do that.
Uh, yeah. That's what I did.
That's very dangerous.
You always have to evacuate.
Right, sure.
Would you like to know the reason I joined the AST?
I would.
But only if you don't mind telling me.
So, the fact that you know about the AST has to mean that you know the reason for the alarms in the first place.
The spirits.
During the fire five years ago, it was actually a spirit that killed your older brother.
But that was...
I kept thinking.
I didn't want more people to have to suffer the way he did.
I wanted to become a person who could protect others from spirits.
She did this because of me.
Can I ask you one more thing?
Yes, of course.
I'm just wondering why you became a spirit.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
What does this mean?
That had to be...
Sounds like lunchtime's about over.
Thanks so much, Itsuka.
I'm glad we were able to chat like this.
Hold on!
Can we talk a little bit more?
But I think class is about to start.
Some other day is fine.
If you're free sometime, can I see you?
Huh?
Like on a date?
Uh, yeah.
I guess so.
Thank you.
Do you think I could have some time to think about it?
Uh, yeah, of course.
Thanks.
Goodbye, then.
So strange, talking to her now.
Am I too used to the other Hurekami?
Shido.
Where the heck did you disappear to during lunch?
Oh, I just got a call from Coterie.
She's fine with curry for dinner.
Ah, that's terrific news.
My mouth's already watering.
Saturday, huh?
Guess I need to have that talk with Ritatusker.
Oh, I'm so tired.
I'm so tired.
I'll just rest a bit.
My goodness.
Huh?
Big boys like you should watch where they sleep.
Dear Shido.
Kurumi!
Last I checked.
Well, that was quite the greeting, wasn't it?
Who knew you had such a cute little sleeping face?
Uh-oh.
What's wrong?
You know, I'm honestly, deeply hurt that you seem to fear me so much.
And here I thought we were comrades who were changing the world together.
Kurumi, do you?
Yes.
I remember everything.
All about the original world.
And about origami, too.
Oh, good.
Then tell me, why did things end up this way?
What happened to origami in this world?
I'm afraid that's something even I'm not aware of, Shido.
However, with origami the way she is now, there are definitely certain ways for us to find out.
Are there really?
Indeed.
Oh, come on.
There's no reason to be so scared.
All I have to do is shoot you to origami.
Once I've done that, I'll be able to see all kinds of things about what sort of life she's lived in this reality.
You have Yud.
That's right.
Then I don't understand.
Why didn't you go ahead and use Yud on origami before, back when she went inverse?
Don't be silly.
Do you actually think I could get close enough to her at that point?
Look, whatever.
Forget it.
Let's do it now.
We can still find out why she inversed in this world, right?
Kurumi, please.
I need your help.
Whatever shall I do with you?
Where could it be?
I don't get it.
How could I lose my hair clip like this?
Wait, what if...
Yes, I knew it!
This is where it was!
Thank goodness.
I should be more careful.
Please, I need your help.
But in that case...
Is that Itsuka's voice?
Itsuka and...
Who?
Origami?
No, this... I can explain.
What's she doing?
One way to find out.
Let's see, how should I greet you here in this world?
Do I say nice to meet you?
Though it does seem quite possible that we've already run into each other several times before this moment in time.
I will kill you.
Armour? I knew it! I knew you were devil!
Satan!
That's a pretty violent way to greet a person.
Don't kill me!
How... how could you do that?
What's the meaning of all this?
Meaning of what?
Itsuka?
What on earth are you doing here?
In a place like this?
Oh...
失礼しないこんでた心 君はそっと拾い上げた
繰り返す日々 どうしようもなく紡いた時
ギュッと抱き締めてくれた
ずっとここで 君と二人で 秒空が流れる
星を見続けたい
君と最後の約束をしよう
世界から私だけ消えてしまっても
気づかれなくていい このままでいたい
刻まれたこの気持ち いつまでも永遠に